phombo.com 2013-05-21

# Privacy Policy | phombo.com

_Last Updated: August 18, 2008_

##### We take your privacy seriously. Please review what we have committed to in order to protect your personal information.

### Overview

The privacy and security of your personal information that we receive and collect from you are important to us. As such, we have set forth certain privacy and security standards that are intended to safeguard your personal information.

This policy covers the privacy practices that apply to all Phombo products and services and Phombo websites worldwide.

This policy does not cover the practices of companies that Phombo does not control, own or work with, or to persons that Phombo does not employ, contract to or manage.

### Information Collection, Use, Sharing and Access

#### 1\. Information Collection

Personal information is information about you that we collect when you register with Phombo in connection with providing you a product or service, or when you voluntarily provide such information.

We may collect information relating to:

  * Credentials such as your Phombo username and password
  * Contact information such as your email address.
  * Browser information such as your IP address, cookies and recorded information such your browser type, language, transactions, contributed content and the date and time of your activities.

#### 2\. Information Use

We may combine personal information collected from you with information from third parties or other companies for providing better user experience and customized services for you.

We may use information for purposes relating to:

  * Customizing the content and advertising that you see
  * Conducting analyses and research
  * Providing/improving products and services that you've requested or that you are most active with
  * Providing anonymous information to internal and external parties
  * Complying with legal processes, subpoenas, court orders, prevent fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.

Phombo may also use information to communicate with you information about Phombo, promotions and products and services. You may opt-out of receiving non-essential communications; however, certain essential emails, which are necessary for the administration and maintenance of your account, may still be communicated with you.

#### 3\. Information Sharing

We do not rent, sell or share your personal information with other people or companies except when we receive your permission.

In the case Phombo is acquired by or merged with another company, Phombo will transfer your information to the acquired or merged company. However, Phombo will notify you before your information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

#### 4\. Information Access

You have the right to view or edit your personal information yourself when you are signed into your account, or have the right to request that Phombo edit the information on your behalf.

For personal information that may not be accessible via the websites, you may still access that information by writing to us by email to privacy@phombo.com, or through our  contact form, and we will contact you within 30 days regarding your request.

You also have the right to limit certain personal information from being displayed on your user profile for the public to view. You may request that Phombo limit the information for you.

We limit access to your personal information to persons under the employment of, contracted by, or managed under Phombo who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with your information in order to do their jobs.

### Links

Phombo may provide, or third parties may provide, links to other websites. Because Phombo has no control over these sites, Phombo cannot acknowledge or endorse the availability, existence or practice of any privacy policies on these external domains. We strongly encourage you to review the privacy policy of these external websites before providing your personal information. At no time will we share your personal information with these non-affiliated domains.

### Use of Cookies

Phombo may use "cookies" to enable you to sign in to our services. Your preference and information may be stored on the cookies in order to simplify your experience by saving you time from repeatedly entering the same information. When you sign in to Phombo using your credentials, cookies will allow you to move from page to page without having to sign in again on each page. When you sign out of, or after 60 minutes of inactivity, these cookies are deleted or expired from your computer.

Cookies may also allow your e-mail address or username be pre-populated, so that you will only need to type your password the next time you sign in. If you are using a public computer or do not otherwise want this information to be stored, you can select the appropriate radio button on the sign-in page, and this cookie will not be used. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.

### Third Party Advertising

Ads may be delivered to you by Phombo or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies, which would allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by Phombo and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

We may occasionally update our privacy policy and respective statement to reflect changes in our products and services. When we post changes to this Statement, we will update the effective date at the top of this statement.

If changes to our privacy policy are material, we will notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes prior to implementing the change or by directly sending you a notification.

We encourage you to periodically review our privacy policy and this statement to be informed of how Phombo is protecting your personal information.

### Questions, Suggestions and Contact

If you have any questions or suggestions relating to our privacy policy and information practice, please contact us at privacy@phombo.com or through our Contact Form.
